alright guys so now we know how to make a very simple web crawler at least a web
好的， 所以 现在我们知道如何 制作 一个非常简单的网络爬虫，至少一个网络
crawler for my cell right here Bucky's room Oryx last trade I'm guessing that
我的手机爬行器就在这里Bucky的 房间Oryx最后一笔交易我猜 这个
you're probably not going to only want to crawl my web page I mean it is pretty
你可能不会 只想要 抓取 我的网页我的意思是它很漂亮
cool but you're probably going to want to let your web crawler do things like
很酷，但你可能会想要 让你的网络抓取工具 做的事情
crawl other web pages start crawling the entire internet and gathering
抓取其他网页开始抓取 整个互联网和聚会
information so instead of just going through page by page by page I'm going
这样的信息，而不是仅仅去 逐页逐页 我要去
to show you guys how to make a dynamic web crawler that can pretty much gather
告诉你们如何 制作动态 网络爬虫，几乎可以收集
links from a web page and crawl those as well so spread out start crawling the
来自网页的链接并将其 抓取为 还有这样 摊开开始爬行
entire web so what I'm going to do is actually build a new function and what
整个网络所以我要做的是 实际上建立一个新的功能和什么
this web crawler is going to do this example is it's pretty much not only
这个网络爬虫将会这样做 例如它 不仅仅是
going to go through page by page but for every item it's in actually go to that
要 逐页而是 要 经过页 它实际上是每个项目
link where the item is and you can actually do a couple different things
链接项目的位置，你可以 实际上做了几件不同的事情
you can either just gather information so say that you're making I don't know
你可以收集信息 所以说 你让 我不知道
maybe a GUI to trade your items well what we do want to do is gather maybe
也许是一个GUI来交换您的项目 我们想要做的就是聚集
the item title maybe some information about the owner so you can either just
项目标题可能是一些信息 关于所有者所以你可以
gather information from the web page or what most web crawlers do is they go to
从网页收集信息或 大多数网络爬虫做的是他们去
that web page gather all of the links from that web page and store them so they can either crawl them later or um
该网页收集所有 链接 从 该网页 并存储它们 他们可以晚些时候爬或者嗯
start spreading out with Karla men's instantly whatever you want to do so I'm
开始与卡拉男人一起分散 无论你想做什么，我都是
going to show you guys both of those techniques and by the end you're going
会告诉 你们两个 人 技术，到最后你要去
to learn how to make some pretty sweet web crawlers so anyways let's go back in
学习如何做一些很甜蜜 网络爬虫所以无论如何让我们回去
here and I'll get myself a little bit more space so again like I said what
在这里， 我会给自己一 点点 更多的空间，如此反复 就像我说的 是什么
this is going to do is go to each item one by one and do something cool with it
这要做的就是去 每个 项目 一个接一个地做一些很酷的事情
so I'm going to name this function get single item data in the parameter that we pass it in is the URL of the item now
所以我要 命名这个 函数get 参数中的单项数据 我们传递的是现在项目的URL
the cool thing about this is we actually pulled the URL from item and it's stored
关于这个很酷的事情是 ，我们 实际上 从项目中提取URL 并将其存储起来
in this href variable so we're going to be passing it in as
在这个href变量中 所以我们要在路过它作为
item URL so how awesome is that like half the work is already done because we
项目URL所以是怎么样真棒 一半的工作已经完成， 因为 我们
already um got the URL of each item in the last Oriole pretty freakin sweet so now with this again the first thing that
已经有了 每个 项目 的URL 最后的 Oriole 非常 好吃 现在这又是第一件事
we always want to do is request the data from the website convert it in plain
我们一直 想做的就是请求数据 从网站 转换为平原
text or in other words just get the source code and then make it into a
文本 或换句话说就是得到了 源代码，然后使其成为 一个
beautiful soup object well check this out as well oh my god this is like the
美丽的汤对象很好检查这个 我的上帝也是这样的
easiest soro ever because everything is basically done for us so again in this
因为一切都是最简单的soro 基本上我们 这样 做了
function as well tired of looking at fantasies say uh I don't know here we go
功能以及厌倦了看 幻想说呃我不知道我们走了
alright so again whenever we're on this page
好的 所以每当我们在这个页面上时
what we need to do is we need to make a new beautiful soup object because the
我们需要做的是我们 需要做一个 新的美丽汤对象，因为
old one was for the search page so in this one we requested that URL which is
旧的那个用于搜索页面 这个我们要求的URL是
now named item URL we got the source code from it and then we convert it to a
现在命名的项目URL我们得到了源 它的代码，然后我们将 其 转换 为
beautiful soup object so now we can crawl it and like pull out links from it
美丽的汤对象，所以现在我们可以 抓取并像它拔出链接
titles whatever we will want so the first thing I want to do is I want to
无论我们想要什么，所以 我想做的第一件事情是我想
show you guys just say you want to gather information from this page so for
告诉你们只是说你想要 从这个页面收集信息，以便
each item will say that you wanted to get like I don't know will get the item
每个项目 都会说你想要 得到 我不知道 会 得到该项目
name and will just get the item name for now I'll show you guys a real keep it
名称， 只会 获取项目名称 现在我会告诉你们 一个真实的 人
really basic so for item name in soup find all actually I can just copy this
非常基本所以汤中的项目名称 找到所有我实际上可以复制这个
right here
就在这儿
what I want to do is get the item name from each individual each individual
我想要做的是获取项目名称 来自每个人的每个人
page now my guess is since it's a new page it's not probably going to have the
页面现在我的猜测是因为它是一个新的 页面它可能不会有
same class because you know it has a different design so let's go ahead and
同一个班，因为你知道它有一个 不同的设计让我们继续前进
find out what information we can use for this all right so the three things you
找出我们可以 使用的信息 这没关系你这三件事
need is what HTML element it is it's a div what attribute are you looking for
需要的是它是什么HTML元素 div你在寻找什么属性
at the class and what's the value of it well I'm just copy this so I don't
在课堂上 ， 它 的 价值是 什么 好吧，我只是复制这个，所以我没有
forget I name so div class I name those are the three things you need whenever
忘记我的名字所以div class 我命名那些 是你 需要 的三件事
you use it so again it's not a link before but the title is now in a div and the class of it is I name which stands
你再次使用它， 它不是一个链接 之前，但标题 现在在div和 它的等级是我的名字
for item name easy to remember so now on each page let's just go ahead and print
项目名称易于记忆， 所以现在 每个页面 让我们 继续 打印
out the item name so I'd name about string remember it takes whatever this
出 项目名称，所以我的名字 字符串记得它需要这些
HTML element is and pulls a string from it or just the text from inside so now
HTML 元素是从中拉出一个字符串 它或者仅仅来自内部的文本现在
what I can do is actually just run this in let's see we actually need to call this right here so copy this and
我能做的实际上就是运行 这个 让我们看看我们实际上需要 打电话 这就在这里， 所以复制这个和
remember right here is basically going through the search page so for each item
记得在这里 基本上是 通过搜索页面， 以便每个项目
actually comment these out because we don't want a bunch of stuff cluttering
实际上是评论这些因为 我们 不要让一堆东西混乱
up our results so basically for each item this href was the URL so go to each
我们的结果 基本上是每个人 item这个href是URL，所以转到每个
items individual page and right now we're just printing out the title of it
单个页面和现在的项目 我们只是打印出它的标题
and actually just so I can test this to make sure it's working instead of
实际上我只能这样测试一下 确保它的工作 ， 而不是
crawling just one page let's curl three so now whenever I run this hopefully
只爬一页让我们卷三 所以每当我有希望地运行这个
it'll work so again what this is doing right now is it's not just going to this
它会再次起作用 现在 不仅仅是 这个
main search page in printing out the titles it's actually going to each of
打印出来的主要搜索页面 这些标题实际上是每个标题
these pages one by one and printing out the titles of each
这些页面 一个接一个地打印出来 每个人的头衔
so check that out and it looks like it is indeed working for more than one page
所以检查一下它看起来像它 确实在为一页以上工作
so again since I know that's working no need to keep going looks good and also I probably should mention this whenever
如此 反复，因为 我知道这是不工作 需要继续下去 看起来不错， 我 也 也许应该提到这一点时
you want to stop your program like maybe you accidentally said crawl 100 pages
要停止 你的程序 一样，也许 你不小心说爬了100页
you just hit this little icon right here stop and also whenever you want to clear
你刚刚点击这个小图标 停止，也可以随时清除
your console you just hit this trashcan clear oh all right so now our web page
你的控制台，你刚刚击中这个 垃圾箱 很清楚哦， 好吧现在我们的网页
orcses me our web crawler cannot only crawl explicitly the pages we told it to
orcses me我们的网络爬虫不仅可以 明确抓取我们告诉它的页面
it can find links then dynamically and crawl those as well now another cool
它可以动态地找到链接 抓住那些现在又一个很酷
thing that you can do is say ok start here find some pages crawl those pages
你 可以做 的事情 是说 行 启动 这里找到一些页面抓取这些页面
well what if you wanted to go to a certain page and find all the links on
好吧，如果你想去一个 某个页面并找到所有链接
this page and crawl those as well well this is actually one of the most common
这个页面并抓好那些 这实际上是最常见的一种
things in web crawlers so might as well show you guys I'd do right now so what
网络爬虫中的东西也是如此 展示你们我现在会做 等 什么
we can do is put for link and I guess we might as well type this out trying to be
我们可以做的是 链接，我想我们 不妨试着这样做
lazy in link in soup fine all now in this case this is actually going to be
现在所有的汤都很好吃 这种情况实际上是这样的
the easiest thing ever we don't need to give it any explicit data we're just
我们不需要的最简单的事情 给它任何明确的数据，我们只是
going to say find all a find all the links on this page so it's going to find this one this one this one this one this
要说找到所有找到所有的 这个页面上的链接，所以它会 找到 这一个这 一个这一个这个
one this one any link that's on the page it's going to gather so um you know it's
一个这 一个页面上的任何链接 它会聚集所以你知道它
actually it's kind of weird that the more work your program does the easier
实际上它 有点奇怪 更多的工作， 你的程序更容易
it is the code mmm funny how things are so anyways now that we have the link
这是代码 mmm有趣的事情 是什么 所以现在我们有链接了
what we can do is just build a complete version of it because if we just look at it like any of these links right here we
我们能做的就是 建立一个完整的 它的版本， 因为我们只是 看看 它 就像 我们这里的 任何 链接 一样
have the same problem before it just links to the arm extension of it and not the base of it because you know let's
它 之前有同样的问题 链接到它的手臂扩展而不是 它的基础，因为你知道让我们
just help people develop websites so of course if we just try to go to this in
只是帮助人们开发网站 当然， 如果我们试着去做这个
our browser it would try to do it on the localhost and not the webpage so build the full
浏览器 它会尝试在localhost上执行此操作 而不是 网页 所以建立完整
version of it and just to make sure it's working we'll print that out
它的版本，只是为了 确保它 工作我们会打印 出
so print href and actually let me comment this out right here so again
所以打印href，实际上让我 再次对此进行评论
what our program is going to do right now is actually don't want to mess up my
什么 我们的节目会做 正确的 现在实际上 是不想搞砸 我的
loops so what our program is going to do right now is say ok this is your
循环所以我们的程序将 要做什么 现在 就说 好了这是你的
starting point go page by page go to each items page in on that page gather
起点逐页转到 该页面上的每个项目页面都会聚集
all the links hopefully that's what it does if I didn't mess anything up so
所有的链接，希望这就是它 的确，如果我没惹什么都涨 这么
that is what it's doing right here and I know this is kind of a it's kind of a
这是它在做什么在这里 和我 知道这有点像
weird example because on each page the links are very similar like I don't know
奇怪的例子， 因为在每个页面上 链接非常相似 ，我不知道
like send a message on view profile so they're going to look the same but what
比如在 视图配置文件 上发送消息 他们会看起来一样但是什么
you can do is if you don't want to crawl the same link over and over again if you
你可以做的就是你 不想爬行 如果你 ，一遍又一遍的链接
guys remember a couple tutorials ago I tell you guys about something called sets now in the example I showed you
伙计们记得几个教程我以前 告诉你们有关的事情 现在在我向 你 展示的例子中设置
guys just a very simple grocery list and you're like ok when the heck am I ever
伙计只是一个非常简单的购物 清单和 你什么时候 我都好
going to make a grocery list piece of software this is the dumbest thing ever well this is one of the instances where
打算做一个杂货清单 软件这是 有史以来 最愚蠢的事情 嗯，这是 实例其中 一个
you can use a set because it's basically a list of items but it has all unique values every item it can't repeat like
你可以使用一套，因为它基本上是 项目列表， 但它具有所有唯一性 尊重每一不能重复 类似项目
you can end a regular list so that way you can throw all of your URLs in a set
你可以结束常规列表，这样的方式 您可以将 所有网址都放在一个集合中
and it will only crow each URL once instead of you know crawling on index
并且它只会破坏每个URL一次 而不是你知道 爬行 索引
each time so that's one cool thing or one cool way that you can use sets to
每一次，这是一个很酷的事情或 一种很酷的方式， 你可以 使用集合
make a very powerful web crawler so anyways that is the very basics of not
制作一个非常强大的 网络爬虫 无论如何，这是非基础知识
only how you can pull information from a single page but also gather the links
只有你如何从a中提取信息 单页但 也收集链接
from those pages then of course you'd say ok now go to this page gather all
从这些页面然后 你当然 说好了现在去这个页面收集所有
the links before you know it you have a million links and you have a next Google
你知道它之前的链接你有一个 百万链接，你有一个下一个谷歌
so that is the basics of making a very simple web crawler if you guys have any questions at all please ask me I'm going
所以这是制作一个非常的基础知识 如果 你们有任何 简单的 网络爬虫 问题，请问我，我要去
to forum also what I is on my forum I posted all the source
到论坛也是 我 在我的论坛上我发布了 所有来源
code so if you go to the forum and in the Python section it is right here 25
代码， 所以如果你去 论坛和 Python部分就在这里25
how to make a web crawler so maybe you have some trouble or you're messing
如何制作网络爬虫所以也许你 遇到麻烦或者你搞砸了
something up then I just copy that and you'll be good to go and also another
什么东西然后我只是复制那个和 你会很高兴去 另一个
thing I want to point out is try to gather this information right here with
我想指出的是尝试 在这里收集这些信息
a web crawler if you can make a web crawler to go to this website and get
如果您可以制作网络，则可以使用网络抓取工具 爬虫去这个网站得到
the source code of how to make a itself that will be the coolest thing ever so
如何 制作自己的源代码 这将是 最酷的 事情 曾经如此
try to do that that will be your next challenge
尝试做那 将是你的下一个 挑战
but for now then guys for watching don't forget subscribe and well
但是现在那些观看的人却没有 忘记 订阅了
see you next time
下次见